# iOS Developer JOHN LIMA

thejohnlima@icloud.com

+55 11
943064948

https://linkedin.com/in/thejohnlima

**೧** thejohnlima

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### PagSeguro UOL

iOS Developer | Since July 2018

Working with native applications using Swift

#### **BRQ**

iOS Developer | April 2017 - June 2018

Working with native applications using Swift and Objective-C

### **Magna Sistemas**

iOS Developer | February 2016 - April 2017

Working with native applications using Swift

#### **Urban Summer**

iOS Developer | February 2015 - February 2016

Working with native and hybrid applications using Titanium, Objective-C and Swift

## **EDUCATION**

Learning algorithms, software engineer, databases, software development in FMU, Sao Paulo, Brazil

System Analysis and Development | February 2014 - June 2018

Learning a lot of concepts about iOS development in Impacta, Sao Paulo, Brazil

iOS Developer | March 2013 - December 2014

# **SKILLS**

Also proficient in web services integration, external frameworks, fastlane, grew up bilingual (Portuguese and English)

Xcode

MVC

Auto Layout

# **About me**

I'm passionate about technology, science, developing things that improve people's lives and make the world a better place. I've been working with mobile development for iOS platform since 2014 with experience on all steps of iOS development, from the concept ofthe ideas until releasing the app on the store and following the results with analytics, tests and crashreports.